Holland mss., 1781-1953 LMC 1575
Lilly Library
- Diaries (Box 6)
  - Holland, Mary Ashby (Todd). Diaries, 1895-1898 (Box 6)
  - Holland, Mary Ashby (Todd). Mexican travel notes, 1938, Feb. 26-Apr. 4 (Box 6)
  - sketchbook, undated. (Box 6)
- Bound volumes (Box 10)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Memorandum book, 1851-1853 (Box 10)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Memorandum book, 1872, Jan 1-1873, Nov 28 (Box 10)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Memorandum book, 1879 (Box 10)
  - Cash book, 1879, May-1881, May. (Box 10)
  - 1894, Sept.-1899, March (Box 10)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Memorandum book, 1895, Jan. 5-1898, Apr. 13 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Hospital formulary., 1897-1903 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Diary, 1897, Oct. 28-1899, May 13 (Box 10)
  - Quarterly abstract of patients. U.S.S. Vicksburg, 1897, Oct. 31-1899, Mar. 30 (Box 10)
  - List of patients, U.S.S. Merrimac, W.O. Stephenson, apothecary, 1898, Apr. 26-1898, June 1 (Box 10)
  - Rough journal. U.S.S. Vicksburg, Norfolk Navy Yard. Washington B. Grove. Assistant surgeon USN, 1898, Sept. 24-1899, May 20 (Box 10)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Memorandum book, 1898, December. (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Pharmacognosy, botany, and materia medica notes, [1898] (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1900, Oct. 1-1901, Feb. 13 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1900, Oct. 9-1901, Apr. 23 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Surgical clinic., 1900 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank., 1900, Oct. 4-1901, Apr. 30 (Box 10)
  - Medical school notes (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1900, Oct. 6-1901, Apr. 10 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1900, Dec. 18-1901, Apr. 12 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Anatomy notes., 1900-1901 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Anatomy notes., 1900-1903 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1901, Feb. 4-1901, May 7 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1901, Apr. 30 (Box 10)
  - Holland, George Frank. Medical school notes, 1901, Oct.3-1901, Nov. 14 (Box 10)
  - Holland, Margaret Ashby (Todd). Revision of a portion of diary of journey to London and British Isles, 1914, June 30-July 15 (Box 10)
  - Holland, Margaret Ashby (Todd). Diary of journey to London and British Isles, 1914, June 30-Aug. 6 (Box 10)
  - Account book of office medical supplies, 1933-1942 (Box 10)
  - Account book, 1937, Jan. 1-1937, July 29 (Box 10)
  - Account book, 1937, July 29-1938, Apr. 14 (Box 10)
  - Account book, 1942, Apr. 27-1942, Aug. 7 (Box 10)
  - Account book, 1904, Oct. 1-1905, Jan. 16 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1905, Nov. 1-1906, Jan. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1905, Aug. 1-Oct. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1905, Apr. 1-July 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1905, Jan. 1-Mar. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1906, Feb. 1-Apr. 30 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1906, May 1-July 25 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1906, July 26-Oct. 16 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1906, Oct. 17-Dec. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1907, Jan. 1-Mar. 22 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1907, Mar. 22-June 30 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1907, July 1-Sept. 16 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1907, Sept. 17-Nov. 30 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1907, Dec. 1- 1908, Feb. 21 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1908, Feb. 22-May 1 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1908, May 27-Aug. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1908, Aug. 21-Nov. 30 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1908, Nov. 24-1909, Mar. 17 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1909, Mar. 17-1909, June 19 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1909, June 20-1909, Sept. 20 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1909, Sept. 21-1910, Jan. 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1910, Jan. 1-1910, Sept. 27 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1910, Oct. 1-1911, Aug. 24 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1914, Feb. 4-1915, May 31 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1915, June 1-1919, June 13 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1919, June 12-1921, Mar. 15 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1921, Mar. 15-1922, Sept. 30 (Box 11)
  - Account book, 1935, Dec. 1-1936, Dec. 31 (Box 11)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Orderly book, 1812-1813 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1869-1870 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1869-1871 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1872-1873 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1876-1877 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1876-1877 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1878-1882 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1883-1884 (Box 12)
  - Ledger, 1883-1894 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1891, Oct. 5-1893, Apr. 5 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1891 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1893, Apr. 8-1894, Aug. 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1894, Sept. 18-1895, Sept. 30 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1895, Oct. 1-1896, July 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1896, Aug. 1-1897, May 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1897, Jan. 1-1898, Mar. 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1898, Apr. 1-1899, Feb. 28 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1899, Mar. 1-Dec. 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1900, Aug. 1-1901, July 1 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1901, Jan. 1-July 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1901, July 1-1902, July 31 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1902, Aug. 1-1903, June 14 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1903, June 15-Nov. 1 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1903, Oct. 23-1904, Mar. 4 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1904, Mar. 4-June 30 (Box 12)
  - Account book, 1904, July 1-Sept. 30 (Box 12)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1886, July 1-1886, Dec. 24 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1887, Jan. 1-1888, Mar. 9 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1887, Jan. 1-1888, June 10 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Jan. 1-Apr. 1 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Jan. 1-May 12; (3 folders) (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Jan. 1-May 19 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Jan. 1-Aug. 28 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Sept. 1-Oct. 30 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1888, Sept. 1-1889, Feb 1 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1888-1889 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1889, Feb. 1-Apr. 1; (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Bookkeeping notes, 1889, March 25-Apr. 8 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Penmanship notes, 1889, Apr. 11-May 1 (Box 13)
  - Holland, George Frank. Penmanship notes, 1889, May 20-30 (Box 13)
  - Chemistry notes. Holland, Ernest Otto, 1892 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1894-1897 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1897-1899 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1900-1908 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1903-1905 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1903-1905 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1904-1905 (Box 13)
  - Ledger, 1905-1907 (Box 13)
  - Chemistry notes, undated. (Box 13)
  - Clinical pathology notes, undated. (Box 13)
  - Philomathean Society, Vevay, Indiana. Constitution and minutes, 1883, Feb. 16-1885, Oct. 1 (Box 14)
  - Holland, George Frank. Indiana University notes, 1891-1892; (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Pharmacy notes, 1893-1894 (Box 14)
  - Organic chemistry, 1894 (Box 14)
  - Materia medica, 1894 (Box 14)
  - Chemistry notes. Holland, George Frank., 1894 (Box 14)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Prescription book, 1895, Nov. 30-[1897], Nov. 14 (Box 14)
  - Osteology. Holland, George Frank, 1897-1900 (Box 14)
  - Anatomy. Holland, George Frank, 1900-1901 (Box 14)
  - Bloomington Ginseng Company, stock certificate book, 1907, Oct. 5-1908, Feb. 8 (Box 14)
  - Statements and collections, 1915-1920 (Box 14)
  - Holland, George Frank. Formulas, undated. (Box 14)
  - Dr. M.H. Shrum. Diseases, undated. (Box 14)
  - Ledger, undated. (Box 14)
  - Clinical pathology, undated. (Box 14)
  - Scrapbook, undated. (Box 14)
  - World War II history of the U.S.S. Mississippi, including reminiscences of men who served on her, ca. 1941-2003; (6 folders, one bound volume, one VHS videotape) (Box 15)
  - Hughes, James. Letter copybook, 1845, Feb. 13-1853, Jan. 10 (Oversize 1)
  - Ledger, 1906-1930 (Oversize 2)
  - Ledger, 1907-1911 (Oversize 3)
  - Ledger, 1911-1915 (Oversize 4)
  - Ledger, 1920-1933 (Oversize 5)
  - Account book, 1911, Aug. 24-1912, Nov. 1 (Oversize 6)
  - Account book, 1912, Nov. 2-1914, Feb. 3 (Oversize 6)
  - Account book, 1922, Oct. 1-1926, May 29 (Oversize 6)
  - Account book, 1926, June 1-1931, July 13 (Oversize 7)
  - Account book, 1931, July 14-1935, Dec. 31 (Oversize 7)
  - Scrapbook, 1860s-1917 (Oversize 8)
  - Scrapbook, 1904-1929 (Oversize 9)
  - Holland, Philip Todd. Scrapbook, 1926-1938 (Oversize 10)
  - Holland, Philip Todd. Scrapbook, 1930s-1940s. (Oversize 11)
- Printed
  - Contains newspaper clippings, mainly fromconcerning the death of Ernest Otto Holland, but also from concerning George Frank Holland's time aboard the U.S.S. Vicksburg; medical journal articles, by Levi Luther Todd., 1950; 1898; 1877-1901 (Box OV 12)
- Certificates, etc.
  - Todd, Levi Luther, Jr. Appointment to office of captain, Washington Guard, 1854, June 27 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Appointment to office of sergeant, Co. H, 6th reg., Indiana Volunteers, 1862, Dec. 21 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Election certificate, auditor of Switzerland County, Indiana, 1882, Nov. 13 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Diploma. College of Pharmacy of the City of New York., 1894, Apr. 25 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Physician's certificate, 1897, July 13 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Physician's license, 1897, July 14 (Box OV 13d)
  - Yearly abstract of patients, U.S.S. Vicksburg, 1899 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Pharmacy license, State Board of New York, 1901, Apr. 30 (Box OV 13d)
  - Todd, Anne D. Diploma from Indianapolis Normal School, 1902, Feb. 10 (Box OV 13d)
  - Bellevue Medical College class of 1903 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank and Margaret Ashby Todd. Marriage license, 1904, June 8 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Certificate of attendance, New Orleans Polyclinic, 1907, Feb. 12 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Military commission, 1912, July 10 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment to first lieutenant in the Medical Reserve corps, 1913, Dec. 1 (Box OV 13d)
  - Documents relating to appointment to Medical Reserve Corps, 1913-1915 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Membership certificate, American College of Surgeons, 1914, June 22 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Membership certificate, Association of Military Surgeons of the United States, 1915, May 25 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment of medical examiner for Aetna Life Insurance Company, 1915, June 28 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Military commission, 1915, July 27 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment to first lieutenant, Medical Reserve corps, 1915, Sept. 24 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment to first lieutenant, Medical Reserve corps, 1916, Feb. 12 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Membership certificate, Association of Military Surgeons of the United States, 1916, June 1 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment to captain, National Guard medical corps, 1917, Aug. 5 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Military commission, 1917, Aug. 11 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Certificate, Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite of Free-Masonry, 1917, Aug. 12 (Box OV 13d)
  - Liberty Class portrait. Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite of Free-Masonry, 1917, Aug. 12 (Box OV 13d)
  - Ancient Accepted Scottish Rite of Free-Masonry. Liberty class, taken in front of Scottish Rite building, 1917, Aug. 12 (Box OV 13a)
  - Holland, George Frank. Appointment to major, National Guard medical corps, 1918, Mar. 13 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Elizabeth. Diploma from Bloomington Junior High School, 1922, Jan. 27 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, George Frank. Membership certificate, Ancient Order of the Nobles of the Mystic Shrine for North America. Murat Temple, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1923, Mar. 24 (Box OV 13d)
  - Hugg, Martin M. and Nancy D. Todd. Marriage license, 1923, Sept. 22 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Elizabeth. Diploma from Bloomington High School, 1929, Jan. 30 (Box OV 13d)
  - Holland, Philip Calphy. Certificate of membership, Indiana State Medical Society, undated. (Box OV 13d)
  - Indiana Field Hospital, Co. No. 21, Hattiesburg, Miss., undated. (Box OV 13b)
  - Todd, Levi Luther. Photograph, undated. (Box OV 13c)